var English = [
  {
    "question"  : "Our government is making determined efforts to eradicate illiteracy.",
     "choice"  : ["compulsory","ineffective", "innocent", "unreliable"],                  
     "correct"  : "ineffective"
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "Makerere University has a large intake of students each year",
     "choice"   : ["rejection", "product",  "output",  "turn-out"],                       
     "correct"  : "rejection"
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "Florence flogged the girl reluctantly.",
     "choice "  : ["eagerly", "calmly", "furiously", "laboriously"],                         
     "correct"  : "calmly"
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "Sola’s car is badly damaged; he has to look for an expert mechanic to fix it.",
     "choice"   : ["uneducated", "amateurish", "awkward",  "unscientific"],                         
     "correct"  : "amateurish"
  },
  
  {
    "question"  : "Coastal plains are often very densely populated.",
     "choice"   : ["weakly", "badly", "rarely", "sparsely"],                        
     "correct"  : "sparsely"
  },
  {
    "question"  : "Wilfredwas a mindless criminal.",
     "choice"  : ["strong", "mindful", "feeling",  "memorable"],                      
     "correct"  : "feeling"
  },
  {
    "question"  : "The judge blamed the plaintiff for misleading the court.",
     "choice"   : ["defendant",  "complainant",  "accused",  "prosecution"],                        
     "correct"  : "defendant"
  },
  {
    "question"  : "The thieves vandalized the vault’s lock.",
     "choice"  : ["repaired",  "arranged", "serviced",  "actuated"],                        
     "correct"  : "repaired"
  },
  {
    "question"  : "The demonstrators have refused to call off their action.",
     "choice"  : ["consolidate", "start", "resume", "end"],                     
     "correct"  : "resume"
  },
  {
    "question"  : "The angry waves swallowed the boat.",
     "choice"   : ["gentle", "unruffled",  "cool",  "serene"],   
     "correct"  : "serene"
  }
  
]